# Arnold Emil Frontend Developer

■ genuine5621@gmail.com

Vienna, Austria

## **Profile**

I'm an experienced front-end developer with a solid background in everything related to online marketing on top. It is my passion to build sleek & well-optimized websites and web apps. I'm very much into gaming and learning to work with new technologies, always improving myself to stay on top of my field. Further, I like nature and enjoy doing some trekking from time to time. Finally, I'm a good person to have a beer with.

#### **Skills**

Responsive Web Design	• • • •
JavaScript & TypeScript	• • • •
React.js	• • • • •
Angular.js	• • • •
Vue.js & Svelte	• • • • •
WordPress & Shopify	• • • •
PHP & Laravel	• • • •
Node.js & Express	• • • • •
MySQL	• • • •
MongoDB	• • • •

# Languages

# **English**

B2

## **Education**

## Bachelor's degree of Computer Science

Vienna University of Technology 2012/01 - 2015/07

+1 803 810 9004

S live:.cid.bcf23391617035d8

# **Professional Experience**

#### Office Manager

Camels

2015/07 - 2017/05 | Vienna, Austria

#### Main areas of application:

Technical infrastructure and website maintenance, office administration and organization, Seminar operation

## Seminar organization:

Preparation of advertising measures (advertisements, banner advertising, print templates), social media support,

Newsletter creation and sending

#### GDPR:

Significant participation in the creation a data protection declaration, processing of order processing contracts

#### Accounting:

Accounting preparation for the Tax advice

# Junior Software Developer

CODERS.BAY Vienna

2017/07 - 2021/02 | Vienna, Austria

# Frontend Developer

Parvan Pajooh

2021/02 - 2022/12 | Tehran, Iran

Worked with advanced web development technologies like React, Typescript, JavaScript, Bootstrap 4, CSS, SASS, and HTML.

Worked with several React UI libraries like Ant design and Material UI.

Created compatible customer client dashboards.

Worked with UX/UI design teams to improve existing applications.

used Jira tool for requirement gathering, GitHub, and Git Lab as version control systems.

used multiple state management like Redux, Context, Recoil

## Frontend Developer

Bühler Group

2022/12 - present | Vienna, Austria